sportsmediawatch.com 2013-11-28

# Sports Media Watch – Privacy Policy

**Privacy  Policy **

Sports Media Watch knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting our website, you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy. 

This Privacy Policy covers Sports Media Watch’s treatment of personal information that Sports Media Watch gathers when you are on the Sports Media Watch website and when you use Sports Media Watch services. This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that Sports Media Watch does not own or control, or to individuals that Sports Media Watch does not employ or manage. 

**Information Collected by Sports Media Watch  **

We only collect personal information that is relevant to the purpose of our website. This information allows us to provide you with a customized and efficient experience. We do not process this information in a way that is incompatible with this objective. We collect the following types of information from our Sports Media Watch users: 

* 1\. Information You Provide to Us: We receive and store any information you enter on our website or provide to us in any other way. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features. 
* 2\. Automatic Information: We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. Sports Media Watch and its authorized agents automatically receive and record certain “traffic data” on their server logs from your browser including your IP address, Sports Media Watch cookie information, and the page you requested. Sports Media Watch uses this traffic data to help diagnose problems with its servers, analyze trends and administer the website.

Sports Media Watch may collect and, on any page, display the total counts that page has been viewed. 

Many companies offer programs that help you to visit websites anonymously. While Sports Media Watch will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these programs are available. 

**E-mail Communications  **

Sports Media Watch is very concerned about your privacy and we will never provide your email address to a third party without your explicit permission, as detailed in the ”Sharing Your Information” section below. Sports Media Watch may send out e-mails with Sports Media Watch-related news, products, offers, surveys or promotions. 

**Cookies**

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our website are visited and by how many people. Sports Media Watch cookies do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are or what your screen name or e-mail address is. 

The ”help” portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. We recommend that you leave the cookies activated because cookies allow you to use some of Sports Media Watch’s coolest features. 

Sports Media Watch’s advertising partners may place a cookie on your browser that makes it possible to collect anonymous non-personally identifiable information that ad delivery systems use to present more relevant ads. If you would prefer to opt-out of this standard practice, please visit our advertising partner Platform-A’s privacy policy and opt-out page. 

**Sharing Your Information  **

Rest assured that we neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone and that we will share your personal information only as described below. 

Sports Media Watch Personnel: Sports Media Watch personnel and authorized consultants and/or contractors may have access to user information if necessary in the normal course of Sports Media Watch business. 

Business Transfers: In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if Sports Media Watch, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred. 

Protection of Sports Media Watch and Others: We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with a law; to enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other policies; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Sports Media Watch, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. 

Syndication: Sports Media Watch allows for the RSS syndication of all of its public content within the Sports Media Watch website. 

With Your Consent: Except as noted above, we will contact you when your personal information is shared with third parties or used for a purpose incompatible with the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected, and you will be able to opt out to prevent the sharing of this information. 

**Children Under  18 Years of Age **

You must be 13 years and older to register to use the Sports Media Watch website. As a result, Sports Media Watch does not specifically collect information about children. If we learn that Sports Media Watch has collected information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. We recommend that minors between the ages of 13 and 18 ask and receive their parents’ permission before using Sports Media Watch or sending information about themselves or anyone else over the Internet. 

**Changes to this  Privacy Policy **

Sports Media Watch may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, at its sole discretion. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes to the Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the Sports Media Watch website so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances if any, it is disclosed. 

**Conditions of Use  **

If you decide to visit Sports Media Watch website, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to thisPrivacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of California state law. 

**Effective Date of this  Privacy Policy **

This Privacy Policy is effective as of May 24, 2011 and last updated May 24, 2011.
